{
  "participantID": "d3d7734f-c406-460f-bf3b-4e2d405bc066",
  "demographicsAnswers": [
    {
      "participantID": "d3d7734f-c406-460f-bf3b-4e2d405bc066",
      "age": 20,
      "gender": "female",
      "experience": "bachelor-inf",
      "englishLevel": "advanced"
    }
  ],
  "score": 9,
  "questionData": {
    "question0": {
      "questionIndex": 0,
      "questionOrder": 1,
      "questionText": "wording change",
      "caseFormat": "kebab4",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "wording-change",
        "wording-chane",
        "wording-chagne",
        "warding-change"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
      "selectedOption": "wording-change",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 27065
    },
    "question1": {
      "questionIndex": 1,
      "questionOrder": 2,
      "questionText": "wording change",
      "caseFormat": "camel4",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "wardingChange",
        "wordingChange",
        "wordingChagne",
        "wordingChane"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
      "selectedOption": "wordingChange",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 6248.20000000298
    },
    "question2": {
      "questionIndex": 2,
      "questionOrder": 3,
      "questionText": "algorithm numbers",
      "caseFormat": "kebab2",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "algorithmn-numbers",
        "algorithm-nunbers",
        "algorithm-numbers",
        "algortithm-numbers"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
      "selectedOption": "algorithm-numbers",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 10638.20000000298
    },
    "question3": {
      "questionIndex": 3,
      "questionOrder": 4,
      "questionText": "jump left",
      "caseFormat": "kebab1",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "junmp-left",
        "jump-left",
        "junp-left",
        "jump-lelt"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
      "selectedOption": "jump-left",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 6216.100000008941
    },
    "question4": {
      "questionIndex": 4,
      "questionOrder": 5,
      "questionText": "packet size",
      "caseFormat": "kebab5",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "packets-size",
        "paket-Size",
        "packet-side",
        "packet-size"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
      "selectedOption": "packet-size",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 8177.0999999940395
    },
    "question5": {
      "questionIndex": 5,
      "questionOrder": 6,
      "questionText": "jump left",
      "caseFormat": "camel1",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "jumpLeft",
        "junpLeft",
        "jumpLelt",
        "jumnpLeft"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
      "selectedOption": "jumpLeft",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 6152
    },
    "question6": {
      "questionIndex": 6,
      "questionOrder": 7,
      "questionText": "query indexes",
      "caseFormat": "camel3",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "queryInbexes",
        "queryIndexes",
        "querryIndexes",
        "quaryIndexes"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
      "selectedOption": "queryIndexes",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 8206
    },
    "question7": {
      "questionIndex": 7,
      "questionOrder": 8,
      "questionText": "algorithm numbers",
      "caseFormat": "camel2",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "algortithmNumbers",
        "algorithmNunbers",
        "algorithmNumbers",
        "algorithmnNumbers"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
      "selectedOption": "algortithmNumbers",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "timeTaken": 9084.90000000596
    },
    "question8": {
      "questionIndex": 8,
      "questionOrder": 9,
      "questionText": "packet size",
      "caseFormat": "camel5",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "packetSide",
        "packetsSize",
        "packetSize",
        "paketSize"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
      "selectedOption": "packetSize",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 5848.5999999940395
    },
    "question9": {
      "questionIndex": 9,
      "questionOrder": 10,
      "questionText": "query indexes",
      "caseFormat": "kebab3",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "quary-indexes",
        "querry-indexes",
        "query-indexes",
        "query-inbexes"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
      "selectedOption": "query-indexes",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 4173.600000008941
    }
  }
}
